amarnatok.com 2012-06-22

# AmarNatok.com - FREE Bangla Natoks, Drama Serials, Ittadi, Recipes! - AMARNATOK.COM - TERMS OF SERVICE & PRIVACY POLICY

AMARNATOK.COM considers that respect of privacy on the Internet is of utmost importance. This statement presents the rules applied by AMARNATOK.COM for the collection and dissemination of personal information given by users on the site. They apply to all "AMARNATOK.COM Sites", i.e. all sites and pages within the "AMARNATOK.COM” domain.

What information is collected by AMARNATOK.COM?

Standard use of the Site

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information. The only information we gather during a general navigation on the Site is the information intended for the server logs: IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, browser type, operating system and information such as the site from which you are connected, pages visited, and the dates and times of those visits.

Collect of Personal Information

The registration of personal information leads to the submission of a cookie* on certain sites of AMARNATOK.COM. By setting this cookie, AMARNATOK.COM will remember your personal details at the next visit so you do not have to re-enter the same information. This helps us to improve the quality of services that we offer.

Participation in electronic discussion groups means that other participants in the group that you have chosen (including those who are not Site Administrators) will be aware of any personal information that you choose to disclose. In some open discussion groups the information is public.

What does AMARNATOK.COM do with the information it collects?

Standard use of the Site

The information collected during the navigation in the "AMARNATOK.COM" area is used to analyze trends and the use of the site in order to improve its usefulness. No personal information is attached there.

Personal Information

AMARNATOK.COM may use such information to:

  * Contact you - either in response to a request or a suggestion, or to send you news, reply, updates and so on;
  * Confirm your entries on the site;
  * "Remember" your online profile and preferences;
  * Statistical analysis performing.

What will happen if I do not want to provide personal information?

Providing personal information on the Site is optional. If you do not want to deliver information of this kind, you can always surf the Site, but you will not be able to access the entire Service and its Information such as placing a request.

Removal or modification of information

You can delete or modify your personal information at any time by returning to the page where you registered them or by contacting the coordinator of the page. If the page in question does not provide any information on this subject, you can contact amarnatok(at)live(dot)com for more information.

If you are not the issuer of personal information that concerns you and want to have it removed, you can send your request to amarnatok(at)live(dot)com

Security

The personal data entrusted to the Site will not be sold or transferred to any third party. Any information provided to AMARNATOK.COM by users of the Site is preserved with the utmost care and maximum safety. It will be used only in the manner described in this privacy policy, or according to the special rules of visited sites or in a manner to which you have explicitly consented. AMARNATOK.COM uses techniques and a variety of measures to ensure the safety of information stored in its systems and protects them from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

The Site provides links to sites outside the "AMARNATOK.COM" area and could not be held responsible for the privacy practices or the content located on them.

* * *

TERMS OF SERVICEPreamble  
  
These Terms of Service describe the terms and conditions under which the administrators of the Internet site AMARNATOK.COM (hereinafter the "Site") provide a service of bulletin board (hereinafter, the "Service"). Access to this Service is subject to compliance with these Terms of Service. Any user of this Service cannot access this Service without having previously been made aware of these Terms of Use and unreservedly agreed to them. They apply to all "AMARNATOK.COM site", i.e. all sites within the "AMARNATOK.COM" domain.  
Site ContentThe information contained on the Website (hereinafter referred to as the "Information"), including text, photographs, images, videos, and messages, is the sole responsibility of its issuer.

AMARNATOK.COM does not guarantee the opportunity, legality, integrity, or quality of the Information.

AMARNATOK.COM is not responsible for the content or accuracy of the Information and reserves the right to correct or amend the mistakes, inaccuracies, technical mistakes, or omissions without notice. In addition, changes or corrections made on the Information may be performed at a different time from the publication time.

AMARNATOK.COM reserves the right to terminate or suspend access to the Site at any time and without prior warning.Hypertext LinksAMARNATOK.COM is not responsible for the content or accuracy of the Information to other sites accessible on the Site, nor is responsible for the existence of a link to this Site on other sites.

A nominal reference to one of these sites or to a service or product does not presume the agreement of AMARNATOK.COM for the content or accuracy. The user assumes all risks associated with its use.GuaranteesThe Information contained in this Site can in no way have a contractual and / or official value.

Accordingly, you agree to use the Information at your own risk. You assume all the costs of any service, repair, or correction needed.

The Information made available on the Site, including but not limited to, Information distributed or proposed in the form of hyperlinks or computer files from other sites, is provided "like the original" without warranty of any kind, expressed or implied.

AMARNATOK.COM does not guarantee that the Information is commercial, that it meets a particular need, that it does not violate any applied rule/law, is free of errors or viruses, or is not of defamatory, offensive, or harmful nature.

However, if your country's law does not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, the preceding paragraph does not apply.  
ResponsibilitiesAMARNATOK.COM is not liable for any direct or indirect incidents (including, but not limited to: loss of data, profits, income, customers, or any other similar economical problem) that might arise from the use of, or inability to use, the Information, the Site, or any linked site.MaintenanceAdministrators maintain the overall quality of the Information and compliance with the rules to the best of their abilities and are in no way (or can be held) responsible for actions and/or comments of other users.Indemnification  
  
You agree to indemnify and guarantee AMARNATOK.COM against any claim or action, losses, and expenses (including court fees) resulting from the violation of the Terms of Service, copyright infraction, or public order troubling.  
Intellectual PropertyYou agree to use the Site in a strictly legal context, particularly in respect of intellectual property law or other related regulations.

AMARNATOK.COM grants you the non-exclusive and non-transferable right to access the Information contained in the Site when you only sign up for your personal use, which excludes any commercial operation at local, national, or international level.

We remind you, in particular, no logo, text, graphics, videos or images contained in the Site could be copied, reproduced, modified, published, issued, posted, transmitted, or distributed by any ways whatsoever without the prior written permission of author or his/her eligibility.

It is understood that AMARNATOK.COM has the ability to use, reproduce, disclose, distribute, and modify ideas, concepts, and techniques of third content and / or exchanged at the Site.

Without prior written consent of the holder of a video protected under intellectual property rights available on the Site, you may not copy, modify, reverse, translate, or create derivative works, transmit, sell, or distribute, directly or indirectly, the design or assembly, or attempt to find the source code (except as provided by law), or transfer any right in relation to the quoted videos/data. In any case, the use of any videos available for download from the Site is governed by the terms of the license accompanying or included in the videos.

All rights to trademarks, service marks and names deposited on the Website are the property of their respective owners, and you are solely responsible for any unauthorized use and / or exploitation.

  * ANY products and company names mentioned in the Site are trademarks and / or services deposited by their legitimate owners. While HTML, graphic design and programming code used in the Site are subject to approval by its author (i.e. the Administrators) before personal use.

LitigationThe TOS and the relationship between you and AMARNATOK.COM are subject to the Law of the Special Administrative Region of the Bangladesh Government. In the absence of agreement, any dispute would be submitted to the competent courts of Bangladesh.

If you are a publisher, producer, author, or distributor of data that the Information refers to outside the Site - or if you are a third person in relation to the above appointments, please provide us with the following documents and send them to us by e-mail at the following address: amarnatok(at)live(dot)com

  * Link to the appropriate page(s) of the Site problematic.
  * Valid reason to demand the abolition of the Information.
  * Evidence and official documents certifying your identity and the link to the data concerned.

Modifications

Any modification of these terms can be made at any time without prior publication or announcement.

Contact

For any questions or inquiries about our privacy policy, you can contact us at amarnatok(at)live(dot)com

*Cookie  
A cookie is a small file that a Web server sends to your browser. It is normally used to assign your computer a unique identification and securely store information: identity of the user, passwords, preferences, online profiles. It is stored on the hard drive of your computer. You can refuse to have cookies delivered by AMARNATOK.COM sites by changing the settings of your browser. Cookies installed in your computer can come from many Internet sites. To protect the confidentiality of data, your browser allows Web sites to access cookies they themselves have sent, not to those that others have sent.
